うわぁ
That bastard!
あいつ
Wait, Bunny!
おい バニー
Damn! Who the hell was he?!
ダッ!  何なんだ あいつは
It's your fault.
あなたのせいだ
Huh?
えっ?
If you didn't stop me back there, this wouldn't have happened.
あなたがあの時止めなければ
こんな事にはならなかった
I was so close to finding out what Ouroboros was.
もう少しで
ウロボロスが何か つかめたのに
H-Hey, calm down.
おい 落ち着け
I can't calm down!
落ち着いていられるか！
They murdered my parents!
こっちは親を殺されてるんだ
あっ
gokigen yo doukashitan darou?
How are you? Is something wrong?
ごきげんよう どうかしたんだろ？
kao wo mireba isshun de wakaru yo
I can tell just by looking at you.
顔を見れば一瞬でわかるよ
senrigan senrigan? messou nai desu
Am I psychic? Of course not.
千里眼千里眼？
めっそうないです
taikutsu GIRL megumaretai no kai
Bored girl, do you want to find happiness?
退屈ガール 恵まれたいのかい
hantei wa shingi no renzoku de
Let's think it through and decide.
判定は審議の連続で
VENUS SUSTAIN
Venus Sustain.
ヴィーナスサステイン
odoru machinami
The city dances.
踊る街並み
PERFECTLY EUPHORIA
Perfectly, Euphoria!
Perfectly Euphoria！
nandemo nai youna kotoba de naitari suru shi
I end up crying over the smallest things.
何でもないような
言葉で泣いたりするし
hora bokutachi nante
Come on, our
ほら 僕達なんて
zentei no nai
temporary passion
juubun tekido ni
lives are
十分適度に
zentei no nai
a temporary passion
DRAMATIC sa
reasonably dramatic.
ドラマチックさ
saikou no wa
the best passion
karuku SUPER STAR
We're almost like super stars!
軽くスーパースター
ORION wo nazoru konna fukai yoru
Looking up at Orion late at night.
オリオンをなぞる こんな深い夜
tsunagaretai hanasaretai
I want to connect. I want to be free.
つながりたい 離されたい
tsumari hanshinhangi acchi kocchi
Basically, I'm not sure and can't decide.
つまり半信半疑あっちこっち
shin mirai wo negau kuuzenzetsugo no
I pray for a new future. The greatest one yet.
新未来を願う 空前絶後の
kotoba ga moshi, moshi tsumugeru nara jikan ga tomaru yo
If I could spin words, time would stop.
言葉がもし もし紡げるなら
時間が止まるよ
koko de owaru hazu ga nai no ni
"There's no way it can end here."
｢ココデオワルハズガナイノニ｣
I get that you have your reasons.
何かしら事情があるのは わかった
But because you lost it,
けど お前がブチ切れたせいで
捕まえることのできた犯罪者が
目の前で殺されたんだぞ
a criminal we could have caught was killed right before our eyes.
それは わかってんな？
Do you understand?
What did that bomber have to do with you?
あの爆弾野郎とお前に
どんな関係があるんだよ
What the hell is Ouroboros?
ウロボロスってのは何なんだ？
We can't do anything if you keep quiet.
黙ってちゃ進まねえだろ！
We don't know what's going on.
俺たちは何が何だか分かんねえんだ
僕だって分かんないですよ！
I don't know either!
Ouroboros is probably
おそらく ウロボロスは
僕の親を殺した犯罪組織です
the crime syndicate that killed my parents.
あ？
What?
爆弾魔の首筋にあったタトゥーが
奴らのマーク
That bomber had their mark tattooed on his neck.
A tattoo?
タトゥー？
あっ
Are you saying that the bomb guy
爆弾野郎が
そのウロボロスの一員だったのか
was a member of Ouroboros?!
But that NEXT!
なのにあのＮＥＸＴが
That's right! What was that guy?!
そうだ
最後に現れたあいつは何なんだよ？
はぁ
Judging from the situation,
状況からみて
真犯人だと考えて間違いないわね
I think it's safe to say that he is the real culprit.
ん？
He's the one behind the recent string of fire-related deaths.
ここ一連の焼死事件
Then the bomb guy wasn't the culprit.
爆弾野郎は犯人じゃなかったってことか
I still can't believe it.
信じらんない
私の発火温度を上回るＮＥＸＴなんて
A NEXT whose firepower is greater than mine...
Wait, what is he trying to do? Who is that NEXT?
あいつの目的は
あのＮＥＸＴは一体何者なんだ？
もう僕には構わないでください
Leave me alone already.
I have no intention of asking for your help.
あなたに頼るつもりはありません
They killed my parents!
こっちは親を殺されてるんだ
Sorry.
ごめんねー
ん？
Did I make you wait?
お ま た せ
Were you able to learn anything?
で 何か わかったのか
Handsome was probably talking about this incident.
ハンサムが言ってたのって
きっとこの事件よ
It's no wonder he's upset.
ハンサムが取り乱すのも無理ないわ
His only lead on his parents' murderer
両親殺しの手がかりが
目の前でムザムザ殺されたんだから
was killed right before his eyes.
Then this killer is...
この犯人があいつの言ってた
Ouroboros.
ウロボロス
But that still doesn't explain that NEXT with the blue flames.
けど分かんねえのが
あの青い炎を使うＮＥＸＴだよ
奴もウロボロスに関係あんのか？
Is he connected to Ouroboros?
可能性としては口封じとか
It's possible that he's doing it to silence people.
口封じ？
Silence?
What do you mean?
どーゆーこと？
にっぶい男！
You sure are dense!
Think about all of the victims of the fire-related deaths.
焼死事件の被害者をよーく考えてごらん
ん？  ん ん
Do they share anything in common?
何か共通点なーい？
They're all criminals!
全員犯罪者
Yes!
イエース
If Ouroboros is a crime syndicate,
ウロボロスが犯罪組織であるなら
then that NEXT might be silencing people in their organization.
あのＮＥＸＴが
組織の口封じをしたのかも
じゃあ 殺された奴ら
全員ウロボロスのメンバーだったの？
Then everyone who was killed was a member of Ouroboros?
Who knows?
さあ？
タトゥーがあれば証明できるかもだけど
Finding that tattoo on them would prove it,
but the corpses are burnt to a crisp.
死体はまる焦げだし
Did you tell any of this to Bunny?
この話 バニーにはしたのか？
それが連絡つかないのよ
Well, I can't get in touch with him.
Great! Barnaby's not even answering his phone anymore!
あーあ とうとう
電話もつながらなくなっちゃったよ
バーナビー君
And I thought he was a dedicated employee,
最近の若者にしては 珍しく
仕事熱心な男だと思ってたのに
which is rare for a kid in this day and age.
What does he mean, he doesn't feel up to it?!
何が“そんな気分になれません”だよ
We're running a business here.
こっちはビジネスでやってんだからさ
About Handsome...
ハンサムさぁ
両親が殺された時ってまだ４つなのよ
His parents were killed when he was only four.
I wonder if he's been dealing with that all by himself since then.
あの子４歳からずっと１人で
それを抱えて生きてきたのかしら
Everyone has their own personal issues to deal with.
誰だっていろんな事情抱えてんだ
I didn't expect you to be so uncaring.
案外冷たいのね あんた
It's not like that.
そうじゃねえよ
This might be a part of Bunny's past
バニーにとっては
簡単に触れて ほしくない
過去かもしれねえだろ
that he doesn't want us to touch.
Honestly!
全く こんな大事な時に
一体何を考えてんだ彼は
What is he thinking in such a crucial time?
Now, now, now...
まあ　まあ まあ いいじゃないすか
It's no big deal.
Even a star employee gets cranky at times.
優等生だって たまには
へそ曲げる事もありますよ
I also had times like that when I was younger.
俺だって若い頃は
そういう時もありました
You were never a star employee to begin with.
君はそもそも優等生なんかじゃないだろ
That's true.
あっ そうかも
You really don't take things seriously, do you?
本当に君は適当な男だね
I'm sorry.
スイマセン
ふーん
Umm... That aside...
あのー それより
Couldn't you find someone better?
もっとマシな奴はいなかったんすか？
ハ ハ ハ ハ ハ…
I had no choice.
仕方ないでしょ
急きょバイトで来てた子をさあ
I had to take the first person who could fill the slot.
I don't think he's capable of filling in for Bunny.
バニーの代わりなんて無理なんじゃ…
Jeez!
もう いきなり呼び出すなんて
失礼しちゃうわ
Calling me out so suddenly...
How rude.
キャー！
ブヒ
Stop! Now that we're—
待て！  俺たちが現れたガッガッ
Hey, you there!
ちょっとそこのアンタ
That's as far as you'll go!
いい気になるのは そこまでよ
ブヒ
ブヒー
ダッ！
Take this!
このー！
You filthy pig!
ブタ野郎！
ブヒー
It's okay now. You're safe!
よく頑張ったわ もう大丈夫だからね
ブヒー
Damn it, they got us! Who the hell are you guys?!
クッソー やられた
一体何なんだお前らは
フッ 俺達か？  俺達
You mean us? We're...
We're the Heroes in this town!
私達はこの町の ヒーロー
ブヒ ブヒ ブヒ ブヒ ブヒ
ブヒ
My name is Blue Rose.
私の名前はブルーローズ
シュテルンビルトの平和は
いつだって私達が守るんだから
We keep the peace in Stern Bild at all times!
そういうことだ
Yeah, what she just said!
My ice is a little bit...
私の氷はちょっぴり
...cold!
コールド
ん？
Huh?
B-But your crime has been put... completely on hold!
おまえの悪事を完全ホールド
Blue Rose!
You're so cool!
イケテルー
You ignored the entire setup!
段取り全部無視しやがって
そんなの知らないわよ
急に呼び出されたんだから
That's not my problem. I was called in on short notice.
Say, did you have a fight with Barnaby?
ねぇ バーナビーとは喧嘩でもしたの？
Hm? Oh, Bunny? It's nothing like that.
ん？  あっ バニーか
別にけんかしたわけじゃねえよ
そっ ならいいけどさ
Oh, okay then.
What? Are you worried about him?
あっ なんだ 気になるのかあいつが
えっ！  そんなんじゃないわよ！
No, I'm not!
Are you sure?
ホントか?
Thank you for waiting!
お待たせいたしました
Coming up next is a surprise concert
続いて我らがアイドルヒーロー
ブルーローズ
by our superstar Hero, Blue Rose!
サプライズコンサートを開催いたします
You heard him. Now get out of the way.
ほら 聞こえたでしょ
さっさと引っ込んでくんない
Hey... good luck!
じゃあ 頑張れよ
誰のために来てあげたと
Who do you think... I'm doing all of this for?!
思ってんの！
Hey. Tiger!
ねえ タイガー
ん？
Huh?
Why didn't you kill him?
何であいつを やっつけなかったんだよ
あいつ？
Him?
That monster was a bad guy, right?
あの怪人 悪い奴だろ
何で捕まえるだけだったの？
Why did you just arrest him?
Why? I arrested him, so isn't that good enough?
何で?  って
悪い奴を捕まえたんだから
それでいいだろ
悪い奴は やっつけなきゃ意味ないよ
Bad guys need to be killed!
イッ！  タタ おんなじとこ
Right on the same spot...
ふぅ
Thanks to you, we had a wonderful charity show.
君のおかげで
すばらしいチャリティーショーに
なったよ ありがとう
Thank you.
Huh?
あー ?
あ
Oh!
あ じゃないだろう
What kind of reaction is that?
Our CEO came all the way to check up on you.
社長が視察にいらっしゃったんだ
Have you forgotten that he is the one
本来クビになってもおかしくない君に
救いの手を差し伸べてくれた恩人だぞ
who saved you from losing your job?
はぁ は あのー
Right. Umm... About that... What can I say?
その節はその なんというか
Hello.
こんちわ
What are you trying to say?!
何が言いたいんだ君は
It's okay, Lloyds.
構わんよ ロイズ君
I'm the one who wanted to thank him personally.
ひと言 お礼を言わせてほしいと
頼んだのは 私の方なんだから
I didn't really do anything.
いえ 俺は別に何も
By the way, Kotetsu, do you have a moment afterwards?
ところで虎徹君
この後時間はあるかな
え？
Huh?
As a sign of my appreciation for your hard work,
日頃のねぎらいの意味も込めて
ぜひ君を招待したい所があるんだが
there's somewhere I want to take you.
あ はい
Oh...
Okay.
いや あのー 招待ってこれすか？
Is this where you wanted to take me?
This is a high-concentration oxygen chamber
斉藤君が新開発した
超高濃度酸素カプセルだ
that Saito has just developed.
まだ試作段階だが
疲労回復には もってこいだし
It's still a prototype, but it's good for relieving fatigue.
いい機会だから
君達に試してもらおうと思ってね
So I thought it would be a good chance
for the two of you to test it out.
"The two of you"?
君達？
Me and Mr. Saito?
俺と斉藤さん？
Bunny! Why are you—?
バニー！  おまえ
マーベリックさんに 呼ばれて
Mr. Maverick called me.
Huh? Mr. Maverick?
えっ？  マーベリック さん？
He's been exhausted lately. It's made him a little nervous.
彼はこのところ
疲れがたまってるようでね
ちょっとナーバスなんだ
そのせいで今日は
君にも迷惑をかけてしまい
Because of that, he gave you trouble today.
I'm very sorry.
申し訳なかった
Well, I don't really mind.
いやあ 別に俺はいいんですけど
How do you feel? Your body feels lighter, doesn't it?
どうだ 気分は？
体が軽くなってきたろ
気持ち良く 眠れそうじゃないか？
Don't you feel as if you could sleep well?
まだ わかんないんすけど
It's still a little early to tell.
Are you getting sleepy? Well? You're getting sleepy now, right?
眠くなってきたかー？
どうだ そろそろ眠くなってきただろう！
Are you asleep?
寝たか！
Well?! Hey, Tiger! Are you asleep?! Hey, how is it?! Answer me!
どうだ！
おい タイガー！
寝たのか おい どうなんだ！
答えろ！
You're so noisy, I can't sleep!
うっさくて眠れねえよ！
Can you hear me, Barnaby?
聞こえるか バーナビー
I can understand your frustrations.
君のやり場のない気持ちは よくわかる
But if you give up now, you won't be able to achieve your goal.
だがここで投げ出してしまっては
君の目的は達成できないよ
I'm sorry for the trouble I caused you, sir.
ご心配おかけして すみません
今はゆっくり休んで
もう一度立て直そうじゃないか
Rest for now, and then we'll try this again.
Yes, sir.
はい
Good night, Barnaby.
おやすみ バーナビー
ハア ハア ハア ハア
もう少しだったのに
I was so close.
Calling Tiger and Barnaby! Report immediately
タイガーアンドバーナビー出動要請発令
現場はダウンタウン地区の教会跡地
急行してください
to the former church site in the downtown area.
Please hurry. I repeat, calling Tiger and Barnaby...
繰り返します
タイガーアンドバーナビー出動要請発令
はぁ
Were you waiting?
いたんですか
It's not a show this time. It's the real thing.
今度はショーじゃねえ 本物の事件だ
I know.
わかってますよ
警察が極秘に追ってた
犯罪組織のアジトをつきとめたんだと
The police found the hideout of a crime syndicate
they were keeping under surveillance.
A crime syndicate!
犯罪組織
Live coverage? It's not going to be a recording?
生中継？  録画じゃなくて？
Isn't it a good idea? We're bound to get high ratings!
グッド アイデアでしょ
高視聴率 間違いなしよ
But they're going to charge into a criminal hideout.
でも アジト突入すんのに
生中継なんかしちゃ
Isn't airing this live like telling them to run away?
逃げてくれって
言ってるようなもんじゃないですか
That's where we come in.
そこが腕の見せ所じゃない
Use your head.
頭使いなさいよ
あ？
Standby?
待機？
ああ
Yeah.
待機ってどういうことですか？
アジトは すぐそこなんでしょ
What do you mean we're on standby?
The hideout is right there, isn't it?
俺だって わかんねえよ
とりあえず待機しろって
I don't know why either. All I'm told is to be on standby.
クー
うーん
We've got permission from the Justice Bureau.
司法局の認可がおりたわ
We'll work with the police,
こちらで警察と連携をとりながら
全ての準備が整い次第
私の指示でヒーローはアジトに突入
and once all the preparations have been made,
the Heroes will charge into the hideout on my command.
同時にＨＥＲＯ ＴＶ生中継スタート
We'll start airing HERO TV live at the same time.
I see.
なるほど
突入と同時なら逃げられっこないか
If we start it at the same time, they can't escape.
ずいぶんスリリングな事を考えますね
What a thrilling idea.
Do you hate thrills?
スリルはお嫌い?
い いえ
N-No, ma'am.
Bonjour, Heroes.
ボンジュー ヒーロー
We know that there are five criminals hiding out in the church.
教会に潜む犯人は
わかっているだけで５名
There's a possibility that they are heavily armed.
銃火器を所持している可能性もあるし
ＮＥＸＴもいるかもしれない
There may also be NEXTs. Be careful.
気をつけてね
The police have sealed off all roadways
すでに警察は万一に備えて
アジト周辺の幹線道路を全て封鎖中
around the hideout, just in case.
Listen up.
いい？
The police have finally tracked this crime syndicate down.
警察がようやくつきとめた犯罪組織よ
You cannot let them escape. HERO TV's reputation is at stake.
ヒーローＴＶのメンツにかけても
絶対に捕り逃がしは許されない
But to put it another way...
でもよく言えば
This is a good opportunity to collect a lot of points.
ポイントを一気に稼ぐ絶好のチャンス
だそうだ よかったな
You heard her. Aren't you happy?
I suppose this isn't the time for points.
ポイントどころじゃねえか
If those guys in the hideout belong to Ouroboros,
もしアジトの奴らが
ウロボロスの一味なら
あの青い炎のＮＥＸＴが現れるかもな
that NEXT with the blue flames might show up.
He's been wiping out criminals.
犯罪者ばっかり消されてるんだ
It's only natural to think
当然
奴を組織の口封じ役と考えるのが筋
that he's silencing them for his organization.
Am I wrong?
違うか
I never would have expected you to think that far ahead.
まさか
おじさんが そこまで考えていたとは
That's what Fire Emblem told me.
全部ファイヤーエンブレムの受け売りだ
I see.
なるほど
I sympathize with your circumstances.
お前の境遇には同情する
はやる気持ちも わかる
And I can understand you feeling impatient.
But remember, a job is a job.
けど 仕事は仕事だぞ
I know that. And I don't need your sympathy.
わかってますよ それに同情は結構です
A job is a job, after all.
仕事は仕事ですから
As always, you're not very cute.
かわいくねえのは相変わらずだな
はい それでは
Yes. Then we'll proceed.
準備ＯＫよ
We're good to go.
今回は特例として
For this mission, I'm making an exception
ヒーロー同士の回線を
全てオープンにする
and keeping all channels open between the Heroes.
了解
Roger that!
Once the commercial is finished, we're on live.
ＣＭあけたら生中継
Go!
ゴー！
なあ バニー
Say, Bunny...
もしあのＮＥＸＴが現れたら
If that NEXT shows up...
あ
What was that?!
何？
おい 一体どうなってんだよ
Hey, what's going on?
Could it be?
もしかして
ん？
It's him!
出やがったな
あー！
He's playing with us!
ふざけやがって
What are you doing, Kotetsu?!
どうする気だ 虎徹
決まってんだろ
Isn't it obvious?
I'm going to save people!
人命救助だよ
Hey, Bunny!
おい バニー こっちは俺達に任せろ
おまえは あいつを追え
We've got this side covered!
You go after him!
Make sure you catch him, okay?!
絶対ふん捕まえてちょうだいね
Yikes!
Damn you guys!
卑怯ども お前ら
Wait! We're here to save you!
待ってくれ 俺達は助けに来たんだ
The commercial is finished.
もうＣＭあけてますけど
中継どうします？
What should we do about the live broadcast?
中止ですよね
Should we cancel it?
続けて
Continue.
ですが！
But...
ここでやめたら
If we stop here, our show will lose its reputation!
番組の信用に関わるでしょ
それに
And besides,
犯罪者を捕まえに行ったヒーローが
逆に彼らを助け出すなんて
Heroes trying to save the criminals
they were supposed to capture...
That's a pretty interesting turn of events.
おもしろい展開じゃない
ふっ
ふっ ふふふ
My fellow Heroes!
ヒーロー諸君 私の声が聞こえるか
Can you hear me?
Hey, what was that voice?
おい 何だよ今の声
構うな 今はこっちに集中しろ
Ignore him! Focus on what you're doing.
The justice you speak of is truly weak and frail.
君達の語る推理は実に弱くもろい
Good Luck!
Good Luck
うわっ
You are pitiful Heroes who cannot save or punish anyone.
救うことも裁くこともできない
哀れなヒーロー達よ
Haven't you realized how useless you are?
まだ己の愚かさに気づかないというのか
I shall show you true justice.
そんな諸君らに
本当の正義を
教えてあげようじゃないか
What's wrong? ls the show over?
どうした もうショーは終わりか
Are you with Ouroboros?
お前はウロボロスなのか
Answer me!
答えろ！
So what if I am?
だったらどうする？
Are you going to catch me and tear off my suit?
捕まえてスーツをはいでみるか
それとも今すぐ八つ裂きにするか
Or are you going to shred me to pieces?
貴様！
Damn you!
What a clear and straightforward answer.
実にわかりやすく明確な答えだ
Don't worry.
安心したまえ
The justice that you and those Heroes
君に限らず
ヒーローの正義など所詮その程度
偽りの正義だ
believe in only goes so far.
It's a false justice.
My name is Lunatic.
私の名はルナティック
I follow my own code of justice.
私は私の正義で動く
I caught you!
捕まえたぞ！  このサイコ野郎
You psychotic bastard!
What you're doing isn't justice at all.
お前のやってることは
正義でもなんでもねえ
It's just murder!
ただの人殺しだ！
Just murder? What an interesting thing to say.
ただの人殺し
おもしろいことを言うね
Not as interesting as your face! There's a glove on it.
おもしろいのはお前の顔だ
グローブついてるぞ
んっ
君がワイルドタイガーか 覚えておこう
So you're Wild Tiger. I'll remember you.
Hey, wait!
おい 待てよ！
あっ
案ずるな
Don't worry.
I will show up again to destroy the darkness of the world.
この世の闇を切り裂くために
私はまた現れる
Damn it!
クッソー またあいつに
He got us again.
It's too early to give up. We still have a lead.
諦めんのはまだ早いぞ
手がかりは残ってる
I got a call from Rock Bison.
ロックバイソンから連絡があった
He managed to revive one of the men in the hideout.
アジトの男が１人
息を吹き返したそうだ
あっ
僕が消え 遠い未来で
boku ga kie tooi mirai de kaseki ni nattara
When I die and become a fossil in the far future,
化石になったら
人は僕に何を見るだろう
hito wa boku ni nani wo miru darou?
what will people see me as?
分析して 名を付けて
bunseki shite na wo tsukete kaidoku wo shitemo
They may try to analyze, name, and understand me,
解読をしても
愛した人は僕しか知らない
aishita hito wa boku shika shiranai
but only I will know the person I loved.
ハロー 生きること
HELLO ikiru koto
Hello, existence.
君の他に 君はできない
kimi no hoka ni kimi wa dekinai
Only you alone can live your life.
輝き続ける 光った星から
kagayaki tsuzukeru hikatta hoshi kara
From the bright star that continues to shine,
輝き続け 光ったあの空から
kagayaki tsuzuke hikatta ano sora kara
from that bright sky that continues to shine.
僕らは何を感じられるだろう
bokura wa nani wo kanjirareru darou?
What can we feel from it?
奇跡は宇宙だけじゃないよ
kiseki wa uchuu dake janai yo
The universe isn't the only miracle.
輝き続ける 光った星から
kagayaki tsuzukeru hikatta hoshi kara
From the bright star that continues to shine,
輝き続け 光ったあの空から
kagayaki tsuzuke hikatta ano sora kara
from that bright sky that continues to shine.
目を閉じたって 閉じきれないよ
me wo tojitatte tojikirenaiyo
You can try to shut your eyes, but you can't shut out your heart.
あの星さえ 持てなかった心
ano hoshi sae motenakatta kokoro
It's something that even the stars did not possess.
どうだ タトゥーはあったか？
Well? Did he have the tattoo?
そっかー あのアジトの犯罪組織
ウロボロスじゃなかったか
I see.
So that crime syndicate wasn't Ouroboros.
もう ジタバタしても仕方ありません
There's no point in making a fuss over it.
彼の意識が戻った時に
また何か聞いてみます
When he regains consciousness, we'll ask him more questions.
なんだ 案外冷静なんだな
What's this? You seem pretty calm.
けど 口封じじゃねえとしたら
あいつの目的は何なんだ
But if he wasn't trying to silence them,
then what was he trying to do?
悪い奴は
やっつけなきゃ意味ないよ
Bad guys need to be killed!
私は私の正義で動く
I follow my own code of justice.
ルナティック
Lunatic...
お忙しい所
無理を言ってすみませんでした
Sorry for all the trouble. I know you're very busy.
いえ これも仕事のうちですので
It's all right. This is part of my job too.
裁判官も大変すねえ
面会の立会なんて地味な仕事を
It must be tough being a judge.
Doing boring work like overseeing meetings...
まあ 裁判官といえど
司法局の役人にすぎませんから
Well, a judge is nothing more
than a civil servant for the Justice Bureau.
また何かあったら 言ってください
But let me know if there is anything else I can do for you.
あなた方への協力は 惜しみませんよ
I will be glad to help.
はーい！
TIGER ＆ BUNNYの
同じ眼鏡を５つ持ってるほう
Hi!
I'm Barnaby, the member of "Tiger & Bunny"
バーナビーです
えっ？  ヒーローキャンペーン
who has five pairs of the same glasses.
Huh? A Hero campaign?
えっ？  このメンツでですか？
What? With these people?
次回　TIGER ＆ BUNNY
There is always a next time
Next time on TIGER & BUNNY:
See you
See you!